Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 3, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Your Job at Cherry-Burrell, Publication (Box 3, Folder 75)
    Author: Cherry-Burrell Corp.
- Box: 3, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: By-Laws of C.B. Independent Union, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Cherry-Burrell Corp. and C-B Independent Union, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Cherry-Burrell Corp. and C-B Independent Union, 1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 76)
    Notes: June 19
  - Item 4: Agreement between Cherry-Burrell Corp. and C-B Independent Union, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Box: 3, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: George Washington's Railroad, Publication (Box 3, Folder 77)
    Author: Chespeake and Ohio Railroad Company- General
  - Item 2: Coal Bin for the World, 1957; Publication (Box 3, Folder 77)
    Author: Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad Company-General
    Notes: Sept
- Box: 3, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Publication (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Box: 3, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Schedule of Wages and General Regulations for Agents Telegraphers, Telephone Operators and Levermen, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 79)
    Notes: No. 10 2 copies
  - Item 2: Schedule of Wages and General Regulations for Trainmen and Yardmen, 1927; Publication (Box 3, Folder 79)
    Notes: No. 3
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Welcome to the Personnel Department, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad Company
  - Item 2: Personnel Policy Manual, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Procedures Covering Transfer of Non-Contract Personnel, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Cross Reference Data, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Visit to Denver Rio Grande and Western Railroad by Messers, Swain & Maccullough, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Career Opportunities for Progress, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Box: 4, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Employees' Pension Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Tuition Refund Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Annual Report, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Annual Report, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Annual Report, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Annual Report, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Annual Report, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: The Chain of Courtesy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: You and the Telephone, 1954; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Annual Report, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Financial summary and supplement to Annual Report, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Box: 4, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Partnership for Progress, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Author: Chessie System Inc.
    Notes: Nov. 25
  - Item 2: A Partnership for Progress, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Notes: Nov. 23
  - Item 3: Chessie/B&O News, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 9 Oct. 6
- Box: 4, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employees Pension Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: Chicago Rawhide Manufacturing Co.
  - Item 2: You and Chicago Rawhide, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Box: 4, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Summary of Final Recommendations of the Training Committee, 1948; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Chicopee Orientation Program
- Box: 4, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: How Employee Traiing Can Help Solve the Production Problems of the Emergency, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Author: Chicopee Manufacturing Co.
- Box: 4, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Rules and Instructions Governing Employees in the Operation of Train Air Brakes and Air Signal, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Author: Chicago Rock Island and Pacific Railroad
  - Item 2: Pension System, 1953; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Box: 4, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Information For Newly Retired Employes, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: Chicago Transit Authority
  - Item 2: Instruction Bulletins, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Box: 4, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Union Leadership Training, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Author: Chicago University
  - Item 2: Objectives, Organization and Program of The Industrial Relations Center, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: "Building Your Union": An Experiment in Correspondence Training of Trade-Union Leaders, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Author: Leonard S. Stein
- Box: 4, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Shall the Rank and File Boss the Plants?, 1946; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Author: Chrysler Corporation
  - Item 2: Didge News Magazine: Golden Jubilee Souvenir Issue, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 29, No. 1
  - Item 3: Chrysler Views, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 5, No. 1 March
  - Item 4: Chrysler Views, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 1 Jan
  - Item 5: Wage Chronology: Franklin Association of Chicago, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: International Shoe Co., 1945-1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Wage Chronology: Chrysler Corporation, 1939-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: How Chrysler Runs a Speaker's Bureau, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Letter, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Author: Douglas A. Fraser
    Notes: Aug. 30
- Box: 4, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: How to Handle Disciplinary Problems: A Manual for Supervisors, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Author: City of Cincinatti
- Box: 4, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Cincinnati Chemical Works, Inc. and Cincinnati Chemical Works Employees' Representative Association, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Author: Cincinnati Chemical Works, Inc.
  - Item 2: Retirement Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Box: 4, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Articles of Agreement between Cincinnati Hotels Association, Inc. and Cincinnati Hotel Employees Council, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Author: Cincinnati Hotels Association, Inc.
    Notes: Jan. 1-Dec. 31
- Box: 4, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Faculty Facts, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Author: Cincinnati University
- Box: 4, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: CITations, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Author: C.I.T. Financial Corporation
- Box: 4, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: 60 Years of Service, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Author: Cities Service Co.
  - Item 2: Expansion and Diversification, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: How to Promote a Depression, 1954; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Service: A Publication of cities Service Company, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Box: 4, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Thrift Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Author: Cities Service Company
  - Item 2: Hospital Surgical and In-Hospital Medical Benefits, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Group Life and Accidental Death and Dismemberment Insurance and Hospital-Surgical Benefits After Retirement, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Major Medical Expense Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: A Look to the Future with Your Cities Service Retirement Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Fellow Employee:, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Notes: Aug. 31
  - Item 7: Retirement Plan, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: Hospital, Surgical and in Hospital Medical Benefits, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: A Look to the future with Your Cities Service Retirement Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1969, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Box: 4, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Statement of Policy and Objectives, 1953; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Author: Citizens Conference on Social Security
- Box: 4, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: You are Important at Citizens: Staff Manual, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Box: 4, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Coalition Calls for Tax Fairness, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Author: Citizens Organized to Restore on Effective Corporate Tax
    Notes: April 10
  - Item 2: Coordinators List for April 15th Actions, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 3: The Failure of Corporate Tax Incentives, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Author: Robert S. McIntyre
  - Item 4: Current Developments, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Notes: April 11
  - Item 5: List of Endorsing Organizations, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 6: AFSCME in the Public Service NEWS, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 7: NEWS AFL-CIO, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 8: National Association of Letter Carriers News, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Author: Vincent R. Sombrotto
  - Item 9: Public Citizen News, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 10: Background on Citizen Action, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 11: Environmental Action: Press Statement Impact of Corporate Taxes on Energy Policy, 1985; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 12: Acorn: Statement at CORECT Press Conference, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 13: Citizens Petition to Restore the Corporate Tax, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 14: Let's Eliminate the Corporate Tax Giveaways: The Case Against ACRS and the Investment Tax Credit, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 15: Corporate Income Taxes in the Reagan Years, 1984; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Box: 4, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Ordinances Governing the City Employees Retirement System, Death Benefit System and Health Care Program, 1956; Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Author: City Employees Retirement System
- Box: 4, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The Pension Fund for City Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Author: City of Calgary
- Box: 4, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: A Letter to the People, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Author: Civil Service Employees Association
  - Item 2: What's In It For Me?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Box: 4, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: A Statement on Supervisory Conduct During a Union Campaign for Recognition, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Author: Clark Equipment Company
  - Item 2: A Statement Regarding Supervisory Conduct when Work Stoppages or Slow Downs Occur, 1961; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Box: 4, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Some Facts About the South Carolina Retirement System, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Author: Clemson University
    Notes: Aug. 1
  - Item 2: Selected Items of Personnel Information for New Employees, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Pre-Retirement Death Benefit Program for Clemson University Employees Who Are Members of the South Carolina Retirement System, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 14
  - Item 4: Credit in S.C. Retirement System for Out-of-State Service, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Notes: Jan. 25
- Box: 4, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Program, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Author: Cleveland Cliffs Iron Company
- Box: 4, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Management Communication, 1954; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Author: Elmer L. Lindseth
    Notes: June 12
- Box: 4, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Interest Charges on Bills Past Due from Retailers, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: Clothing Manufacturers Association of the USA
  - Item 2: History of Men's Clothing Industry, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: Harry Cobrin
  - Item 3: CMA Double Header "How To " Seminar on Solving Problems wih Tailored KnitsSetting Up Your Own Engineering Dept., 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Notes: March 13
  - Item 4: New Fashion Newsletter Designed to Bring Dual Message to Nation's Clothing Retailers, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Item 5: Your Participation in Shipping Locaiton Survey Needed for CMA Protest vs. Carriers' Limiting their Liability, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Author: Robert A. Kaplan
  - Item 6: Highlights of February 16, 1971 Meeting of CMA Board of Directors, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Box: 4, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The Coleman Company-Yesterday and Today, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Author: Coleman Company Inc.
  - 1975, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Box: 4, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Benefit Program, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Author: Colgate University
  - Item 2: Benefit Program, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Box: 4, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Building Your Future, Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Author: Colonial Stores Inc.
- Box: 4, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Your Job with CW, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
    Author: Colonial Williamsburg
- Box: 4, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Colorado Employment Security Act, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    Author: Colorado Dept. of Employment
- Box: 4, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Know Your Colorado Retirement Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
    Author: Colorado Public Employees Retirement Board
- Box: 4, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The CUE, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Author: Colorado University
    Notes: Vol. 20, No. 1 Sept.
- Box: 4, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Forests Ever Green-Ever Growing, Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Author: Columbia Cellulose Co.
- Box: 4, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Reporter, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Author: Columbia Gas System, Inc.
  - Item 2: Milepost, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Notes: Vol. 23 No. 2
  - Item 3: On Stream, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
    Notes: Vol. 17, No. 3
  - Item 4: Columbia Today, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Box: 4, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Columbia Southern Chemical Corp. and Independent Chorme Workers Association, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Author: Columbia Southern Chemical Corp.
    Notes: March 15, 1955
- Box: 4, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Colson Handbook, Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Author: U. O. Colson Co.
  - Item 2: Recruiting and Selecting Manual, Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: A Colson Career and What it Means to You!, 1956; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Box: 4, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Box: 4, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Employee Manual, 1956; Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Author: Combustion Engineering Inc.
- Box: 4, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Management and Merit Employment, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Author: Commerce and Industry Association
- Box: 4, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Labor's Aims in War and Peace, 1944; Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Author: Amy Hewes
- Box: 4, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Mid Year Annual Wage Letter, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Author: Edward A. Rumely
- Box: 4, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: The Right Way to Provide Security Against Illness andOld Age, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
    Author: Willford I. King
- Box: 4, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Health Security News, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Author: Committee for National Health Insurance
    Notes: Vol. 4, No. 3 April 14
  - Item 2: CNHI, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Item 3: CNHI, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Item 4: CNHI, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Item 5: Health Security News, 1974; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 1 Jan.
  - Item 6: National Health Insurance Newsletter, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    Notes: Vol. 1, No. 1 Feb.
- Box: 4, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Directory of Union-Sponsored Health Centers and Medical Service Programs, 1953; Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
    Author: Committee for the Nation's Health
- Box: 4, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Trade or Fade, Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Author: Committee for a National Trade Policy
- Box: 4, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Watt's Happening, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
    Author: Commonwealth Edison Co.
    Notes: Vol. 3, No. 19 Oct. 15
- Box: 4, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Employe Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Box: 4, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Research Note, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Author: Community Council of Greater New York
    Notes: Jan. 17
  - Item 2: Check Points, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Notes: Jan. 31
  - Item 3: Research Note, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 51)
    Notes: Jan. 27
- Box: 4, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Program and Development, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 52)
    Author: Community Health Association
  - 1957, Publication (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Box: 4, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: The People Take the Lead, 1947-1952 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    Author: Community Relations Services
  - Item 2: FEPC-How it Works in Seven States, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Item 3: School Calendar, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    Notes: Sept. 1951-Aug. 1952
- Box: 4, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Worker Participation: New Voices in Management, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 54)
    Author: The Conference Board
  - Item 2: Nondiscrimination in Employment: Changing Perspectives 1963-1972, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Box: 4, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Conference Notes, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Author: The Conference of Professional Tech. Personnel
    Notes: Vol. 29, No. 2 April
  - Item 2: Conference Notes, 1977; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Notes: Vol. 29, No. 1 April
  - Item 3: Conference Notes, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Notes: Vol. 28, No. 1 July
  - Item 4: conference Notes, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Notes: Vol. 28, No. 2 Nov.
  - Item 5: Conference Notes, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Notes: Vol. 27, No. 2 Aug.
  - Item 6: Vol. 27, No. 1 June, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Item 7: The Special 1975 Personnel Adjustment Program A Joint CPTP/ACT Position Paper, Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Item 8: Conference Notes, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Notes: Vol. 22, No. 1 Feb.
  - Item 9: Conference Notes, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Notes: Vol. 21, No. 3 Oct.
  - Item 10: Conference Notes, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    Notes: Vol. 21, No. 2 June
- Box: 4, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Social Insurance Program, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 56)
    Author: Colorado Fuel and Iron Co.
  - Item 2: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Item 3: Social Insurance Program, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Box: 4, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Industrial Representation Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Item 2: Industrial Bulletin, 1928; Publication (Box 4, Folder 57)
    Notes: Vol. 8, No. 1 Jan.
  - Item 3: The Colorado Industrial Plan, 1916; Publication (Box 4, Folder 57)
    Author: John D. Rockefeller Jr.
- Box: 4, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Disputes Procedures, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Author: Confederation of British Industry
- Box: 4, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: The Supervisor and Collective Bargaining, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 59)
    Author: Congoleum-Nairn Company
  - Item 2: Prevention of Grievances, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Box: 4, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Board of Mediation and Arbitration Observes 60th Anniversary 1985-1955, Publication (Box 4, Folder 60)
    Author: Connecticut Board of Mediation and Arbitration
  - Item 2: Monthly Bulletin, Publication (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Box: 4, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Commission on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Author: Connecticut Commission on Civil Rights
    Notes: Reprinted from 1961-1962 Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor
  - Item 2: Commission on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Notes: Report from the 1962-1963 Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor
  - Item 3: Commission on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Notes: Reprinted from the 1963-1964 Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor
  - Item 4: Commission on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Notes: Reprinted from the 1964-1965 Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor
  - Item 5: Commission on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Notes: Rerinted from the 1958-1959 Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor
  - Item 6: Commission of Civil Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Notes: Reprinted from the 1965-1966 Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor
  - Item 7: Commission on Civil Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Notes: Reprinted fron the 1959-1960 Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor
  - Item 8: Commission on civil Rights, Publication (Box 4, Folder 61)
    Notes: Reprinted from the 1961-1962 Digest of Connecticut Administrative Reports to the Governor
- Box: 4, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Policies and Procedures for Unclassified Personnel, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 62)
    Author: Connecticut Department of Education
- Box: 4, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Letter Notes and Quotes, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Author: Connecticut General Life Insurance
    Notes: June 15
  - Item 2: Notes and Quotes, 1974; Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Notes: No. 410 Sept.-Oct.
  - Item 3: Notes and Quotes, 1974; Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Notes: No. 411 Nov.-Dec.
  - Item 4: Notes and Quotes, 1974; Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Notes: No. 415 May-June
  - Item 5: Notes and Quotes, 1974; Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Notes: No. 413 Jan.-Feb.
  - Item 6: Notes and Quotes, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 63)
    Notes: No. 408 June-July
- Box: 4, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Connecticut General Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 64)